From the darkness, the ultimate fighter rises.
Jiu Jitsu is a action, science fiction, fantasy
film directed by Dimitri Logothetis.
Every six years, an ancient order of jiu-jitsu fighters joins
forces to battle a vicious race of alien invaders.
But when a celebrated war hero goes down in defeat, the fate of
the planet and mankind hangs in the balance.
Jake, played by Alain Moussi.
Wylie, played by Nicolas Cage.
Kueng, played by Tony Jaa.
Carmen, played by JuJu Chan.
Tex, played by Eddie Steeples.
Myra, played by Marie Avgeropoulos.
Jiu Jitsu is a 2020 American science fiction martial arts film directed by
Dimitri Logothetis, who co-wrote the screenplay with James McGrath.
It is based on the 2017 comic book of the same name by Logothetis and McGrath.
It stars Alain Moussi, Frank Grillo, JuJu Chan, Tony Jaa and Nicolas Cage.
It was a box office bomb, grossing less than $100,000 against a
budget of $25 million, and was critically panned.
The film explores themes of martial arts, based on comic, jiu-jitsu.
The tone is thought_provoking.